

Arda Gürel

Geneticist | Photographer | Aspiring Data Scientist

About Me

Master's degree in Molecular Bioengineering from Dresden Technical University. Speaking English and German. Research experience in cancer, and tissue engineering fields. Currently working as a clinical research coordinator within the Düzen Laboratories Group. Improving my coding and data science skills.

Bio

28

☑ Email

ardagurel@live.com

Phone

+90 538 673 95 93

Address

Şişli, İstanbul

Professional Skills

MS Office

Data Analysis

ADVANCE

Project Management

ADVANCE

Python

ADVANCE

Tableau

INTERMEDIATE

Web Development

Work Experience

Clinical Coordinator at Düzen Laboratories Group

Mar, 2020 - Present

Managing clinical research projects and sponsored patient support programs. Analyzing the cumulative data and creating reports.

Moderator at Arvato Bertelsmann

May, 2018 - May, 2019

Editing content in English and Turkish.

Researcher at Corbeil Lab / BIOTEC

Jan, 2011 - May, 2013

Completed the cell culture and staining experiments necessary for my masters' thesis in Corbeil lab.

Education

Masters in Molecular Bioengineering from Dresden Technology University
2015 - 2017

My thesis subject was the existence of primary cilia in anchorage-dependent epithelial cancer and leukemia cells.

Bachelor of Genetics and Bioengineering from Yeditepe University
2011 - 2015

My thesis subject was optimization of porous sponge cell-scaffolds to be used in tissue engineering applications against neurodegenerative diseases.

Science Studies from Istek Atanur Oğuz Lisesi

2007 - 2011

Studied with success scholarship.

Contact

0538 673 95 93

 oxdot ardagurel@live.com